Guide to the Mary Butts Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Papers of Camilla Bagg spans the years 1930-90, and is organized under three headings: Correspondence, Writings, and Other Papers. Correspondence is organized under two subheadings: Family Correspondence and General Correspondence.
Family Correspondence spans the years 1930-36, and includes letters from Mary Butts, Mary Colville-Hyde, and Ada Briggs. General Correspondence spans the years 1931-89, and largely concerns the literary legacy of Mary Butts, including Yale University's attempts to acquire her papers in the 1950s-60s. Correspondence concerning the fate of the papers includes letters from Butts's literary executor Angus Davidson, her friend Harcourt Wesson Bull, and the family solicitors, Warren Murton Foster & Swan, as well as from Robert Gathorne-Hardy and Sir Nikolaus Pevsner, from whom Camilla sought advice. Other letters are from researchers interested in Mary Butts or the Butts family. Chief among these is Robert H. Byington, who began research for a biography on Mary Butts in the early 1960s and became very friendly with Camilla. The two maintained an extensive correspondence until the early 1980s; their falling out is described in detail in Camilla's essay "A Literary Friendship," which can be found below under the heading Writings (Box 16, Folder 225). Copies of Camilla's outgoing letters to Byington are present throughout their correspondence; they document her feelings about her mother, family history, and her own life as an adult. Other researchers include Louis Adeane, G. E. Bentley, Stanley Revell, and Herbert Frank Ingram; Camilla's correspondence with Ingram can be found in Series III, Papers of Others (Box 21, Folder 313).
Writings contains a single long essay. Camilla Bagg wrote "A Literary Friendship" in the 1980s, following a conference on Mary Butts at the University of California, Davis, in 1984. This document focuses on the deterioration of Camilla's trust in Robert H. Byington, to whom she had given almost exclusive access to Butts's papers while he worked on his biography. However, it is also her explanation and justification for not having made the papers more widely avaliable when they came into her possession in 1945.
Other Papers contains a partial transcript of the 1984 U. C. Davis conference "Mary Butts: Her Writings and Her World;" photographs of Butts's gravestone; auction catalogs from the sales of Butts family items between 1932 and 1966; clippings Camilla had placed in Mary Butts's notebooks; and a chart showing which real Butts, Briggs, and Colville-Hyde family members correspond with fictional characters in Curious Relations, a novel by Anthony Butts that was published under the pseudonym William D'Arfey.
Papers of Ada E. Briggs contains Correspondence and Other Papers. It includes substantial files of letters from Mary Butts, Camilla Rodker, Mary Colville-Hyde, and John Rodker, as well as a few letters from other people important in Mary Butts's life, such as Gabriel Atkin, Cecil Maitland, and Angus Davidson. Also present are financial records concerning Camilla Rodker and money lent or given to Mary Butts; a copy of the auction catalog from the sale of Salterns in 1923, annotated to show which items she or her sisters bought back for the family; a clipping of a news photo showing Salterns after it burned in 1950; and an annotated copy of "In a Bombed House: an Elegy in Memory of Anthony Butts," by William Plomer, into which is tipped "A Catalogue of Some of Blake's Pictures at The Salterns."
Papers of Anthony Butts consists of two incomplete drafts of plays, titled "Iphigenia in Argos" and "Dora Jordan, or, the Comic Muse," and one incomplete draft of a letter to an unidentified recipient.
Butts Family Papers contains a Butts genealogy and a leaf from a family Bible inscribed with genealogical information. The first item, "Pedigree of the Family of Butts," is a bound typescript genealogy covering 1260-1890, with additional manuscript entries up to 1930, and manuscript annotations throughout by Mary Colville-Hyde, as well as a few annotations by Camilla Rodker Bagg. The "Pedigree" was discovered in a second-hand bookshop and given to Camilla by Herbert Frank Ingram in the 1960s, but appears to have been made for or by Captain F. J. Butts in the 1890s. The leaf from the Bible contains information about the family of F. J. Butts's uncle Joseph Edward Butts and his wife Sarah. It lists the births of their children, 1805-1821, and contains an 1830 inscription to Sarah Butts. This leaf was originally stored in the Bible of Thomas Butts (1759-1846), F. J. Butts's grandfather and Blake's patron, which has been cataloged separately. That Bible is inscribed with family information from 1784-1890, its last entry recording the birth of Mary Franies Butts.
Papers of Mary Colville-Hyde contain Correspondence, Writings, and Other Papers. Correspondence includes letters from Camilla Rodker, Sir Hickman Beckett Bacon, and Keith Miller Jones, as well as outgoing letters to Anthony Butts, her mother Sarah Briggs, and the Butts family solicitors. Also present is the printed version of an article Colville-Hyde wrote about Holbein portraits of Sir William and Lady Butts owned by the Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum in Boston, printed in Apollo in 1935. Her Other Papers include a copy of her will and printed articles regarding the restoration of the supposed Holbein portrait of Sir William Butts that the family sold to the Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, in the 1930s.
The selection of John Rodker's correspondence that was given to Camilla Bagg by her older half-sister Joan, Rodker's daughter from a liaison with Sonia Cohen before his marriage to Butts, concerns only Camilla and Mary Butts, and spans the years 1921-37. It includes correspondence with Camilla, Ada Briggs, Mary Butts, Mary Colville-Hyde, and Rodker's and Butts's solicitors. Rodker's correspondence with Mary Butts spans the years ca. 1926-36, and chiefly concerns arrangements for Camilla, but several of Butts's letters give news of herself and mutual friends, and a few touch on Rodker's publishing ventures. Correspondence with solicitors firms concerns Rodker's divorce from Mary Butts and their legal settlement over Camilla, in which Mary Colville-Hyde agreed to pay a portion of Camilla's expenses. Correspondence with Mary Colville-Hyde largely concerns this arrangement, and his related efforts in the 1930s to help her sell the painting believed to be by Holbein; included here is a copy of a history of the painting written by Mary Colville-Hyde. Correspondence with Ada Briggs chiefly concerns Camilla, but a few letters discuss Rodker's relationship with Mary Butts. Rodker's active interest in Camilla's well-being is further documented in his correspondence with schools, doctors, and others in whose care she was placed. Copies of Rodker's outgoing letters can be found throughout his correspondence. Rodker's papers also include one folder of notes concerning Camilla.
The final subseries, Photographs and Artwork, contains family photographs from the 1880s through 1926, including photographs of Mary Butts from childhood through her marriage to Rodker; photographs of Mary Colville-Hyde and Ada Briggs in their youth and in their later years, including one showing Ada Briggs as Poole's first Councilwoman, ca. 1920, and a photograph of a portrait of Ada by Irlam Briggs from the same time; a photograph of a portrait minature of Captain F. J. Butts painted circa 1860; and a photograph of the family together on Captain Butts's yacht in the 1890s. Artwork includes two portraits of Mary Butts by her aunt Irlam Briggs, both showing her in her teens or twenties; one is a watercolor, the other an oil painting of her as St. Cecilia.
Series III, Papers of Others (Boxes 21-22), contains a draft of a biography of Butts by Robert H. Byington, and research files about Butts compiled by Herbert Frank Ingram and Stanley Revell, which Camilla Bagg eventually acquired. Robert Byington's extensive draft for his biography, "The Quest for Mary Butts" (1981), is a narrative description of his twenty years of research on Butts. It includes accounts of interviews and correspondence with a number of Butts's friends and contemporaries, including Virgil Thomson, Rebecca West, Glenway Wescott, and many others. It also describes Byington's use of Butts's papers and his friendship with Camilla Bagg.
Also in this series are the research files and related correspondence of Herbert Frank Ingram, a Dorset writer who wrote about Mary Butts for the Poole and Dorset Herald and tried to have a longer biographical article about her published as part of a series of pamphlets about famous Dorset people. Both the newspaper article and the longer sketch are included here, as is his correspondence with Camilla Bagg, incoming and outgoing, from 1966-84, and with his friend Harry Johnstone, who did much research for him on Mary Butts. Ingram's research files include copies of articles about Butts by other writers, excerpts from memoirs and articles in which Butts is mentioned, printed book reviews by Butts, and reviews of her writings as well as reviews of Anthony Butts's and William Plomer's fictional treatments of the family. There is an extensive file on the Butts and Briggs families, which includes information about the Butts family from the middle ages through the twentieth century, as well as clippings documenting the deaths of Irlam and Ada Briggs and a financial scandal in which Mary Colville-Hyde was a victim. Ingram's files also include copies of the death certificates of Mary Butts and her brother Anthony; the dust jacket for the 1933 Wishart edition of Mary Butts's novel Ashe of Rings; photographs of Salterns; and copies of drawings of Mary Butts.
This series also includes one folder of research notes on Mary Butts and John Rodker compiled by Stanley Revell. It contains his notes from several interviews with Camilla Bagg in the 1980s, as well as information from other sources.
Appendix: Butts Family
Thomas Butts (1759-1846) (Blake's patron) m. Elizabeth Cooper
----William Hardwick Butts (b. 1791)
----George Butts (b. 1792)
----Joseph Edward Butts (b.1784) m. Sarah
--------Thomas Butts (b. 1805)
--------Edward Herringham Butts (b. 1810)
--------Henry Wellington Halse Butts (b. 1812)
--------William George Butts (b. 1814)
--------Elizabeth Butts (b. 1818)
--------Charles Napoleon Butts (b. 1821)
----Thomas Butts, Jr. (1788-1862) m. Mary Ann Barrow
--------Emily Butts (died young)
--------Aubrey Thomas Butts (died in India)
--------Charles Edmund Butts (died in Paris)
--------Clara Frances Butts (died young)
--------Mary Ann Blanche Butts (b. 1844) m. G. E. Graham Foster Pigott
------------George Edward Graham Foster Pigott
------------Aubrey Graham Foster Pigott (d. 1865)
------------Mary Graham Foster Pigott
-------- Frederick John Butts (1833-1905) m. Eleanor Stanbridge (d. 1888)
------------Cecil Aubrey Tilbrook Butts (1861-1885)
------------John Mortimer Craven Butts (1867-1868)
* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * 2nd. m. Mary Jane Briggs (1863-1944)
------------ Anthony Bacon Drury Butts (1901-1941)
------------ Mary Franies Butts (1890-1937) m. John Rodker (1894-1955)
* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * 2nd. m. Gabriel Atkin (1897-1937)
---------------- Camilla Elizabeth Rodker (1920- ) m. H. Israel (d.1950s)
* * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * * 2nd. m. Reginald Bagg
--------------------Daniel Israel (b. ca. 1949)
--------------------Edward Israel (b. ca. 1951)
Authors, British -- 20th Century -- Archives; British literature -- 20th Century; Conscientious objectors -- Great Britain; English literature -- Classical influences; Magic; Modernism (Literature); Occultism; Women authors, English -- 20th Century; World War, 1914-1918 -- Social aspects -- Great Britain; Paris (France) -- Intellectual life; Diaries; Drawings (visual works); Paintings (visual works); Photograph albums; Photographic prints; Atkin, Gabriel, 1897-1937; Bagg, Camilla Rodker, 1920-; Briggs, Ada E., 1861-1951; Briggs, E. Irlam (Emma Irlam), 1867-1951; Butts, Anthony, 1901-1941; Butts, Frederick John, 1833-1905; Butts, Mary, 1890-1937 -- Archives; Butts, Thomas, 1759-1846; Byington, Robert H.; Cocteau, Jean, 1889-1963; Colville-Hyde, Mary, 1863-1944; Davidson, Angus, 1898-1982; Forster, E. M. (Edward Morgan), 1879-1970; Ingram, Herbert Frank, -1984; Joyce, James, 1882-1941; Lindsay, Jack, 1900-1990; Lynes, George Platt, 1907-1955; Maitland, Cecil, d. 1926; Mayne, Ethel Colburn, -1941; Pound, Ezra, 1885-1972; Revell, Stanley; Roberts, R. Ellis (Richard Ellis), 1879-1953; Rodker, John, 1894-1955; Ross Williamson, Hugh, 1901-1978; Royde-Smith, Naomi, 1875-1964; Sinclair, May, 1863-1946; Wescott, Glenway, 1901-1987; Williams, Charles, 1886-1945; Butt family
- Papers of Mary Butts, [ca.1900]-37; Series I; 6.3; (15 boxes)
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Family Correspondence
      - Atkin, Gabriel, 1928, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
        Scope and Contents
        Includes one small photograph of Atkin and one news clipping photo of him, glued to letters
      - Bagg, Camilla Rodker, [ca. 1928]-32 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Briggs, Sarah, [ca. 1900] (Box 1, Folder 3)
        Outgoing letter from MB
      - Butts, Anthony, [ca. 1923-36] (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Butts, Frederick John, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Colville-Hyde, Mary, [1928-32] (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Rodker, John, 1929-32, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence
      - Auric, Georges, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Baker, G. P. (George Philip), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Barnes, Djuna, 1937 Feb 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Bax, Clifford, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - The Bookman
        Related Archival Materials note
        See: Ross Williamson, Hugh Box 1, Folder 36
      - Borenius, Tancred, 1932 Mar 4 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Broadbent, Una, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Cocteau, Jean, 1926-29, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - The Cornhill Magazine, 1934-36 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Coryn, M. S., 1933 Nov 26 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - The Criterion, 1932, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Damon, S. Foster (Samuel Foster), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Davenport, John, 1932 Dec 12 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Desbordes, Jean, 1928 Aug 18, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Dusany, Edward John Moreton Drax Plunkett, Baron, 1936 Jan 11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Eliot, T. S. (Thomas Stearns)
        See: The Criterion, Box 1, Folder 18
      - Ellis, Havelock, [1935 Jan] (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Forster, E. M. (Edward Morgan), 1932-35 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Garnett, Edward, 1916 Jul 15 (Box 1, Folder 25)
        Salutation is "Dear Sanger"
      - Goldring, Douglas, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Goodyear, R. G., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - James, M. R. (Montague Rhodes), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Joyce, James, 1921 Nov 7, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Lewis, Wyndham, 1920 Apr 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Lindsay, Jack, 1934-37 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Mayne, Ethel Colburn, 1922-35 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Pound, Ezra, 1931 Dec 2, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Pryce-Jones, Alan, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Roberts, R. Ellis (Richard Ellis); Roberts, Harriet, 1933-36 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Ross Williamson, Hugh, 1931-34 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Royde-Smith, Naomi, 1933-35 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Sackville-West, Edward, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Simpson, Helen, 1935 Jan 10 (Box 2, Folder 39)
        Addressed to Methuen & Co.
      - Sinclair, May, 1920 Jan 7 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Symons, A. J. A. (Alphonse James Albert), 1934-35 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Wells, H. G. (Herbert George), 1928 Feb 26 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Wescott, Glenway, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Wickham, Anna, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Wilkinson, Louis, 1932 Aug 27 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Williams, Charles, 1934-37 (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Wishart & Co., 1932 Dec 5 (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Van Vechten, Carl, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Young, Filson, 1932 Nov 28 (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Other correspondents, 1916-36, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - WRITINGS
    - Notebooks
      - Volume 1: July 21 to September 30, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - Volume 2: October 1 to December 2, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - Volume 3: December 3, 1916 to May 7, 1917, 1916-17 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Volume 4: September 18, 1917 to July 4, 1918, 1917-18 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - July 7 to 14, 1918
        See: Plays, "Fantasia," Box 11, Folder 169
      - Volume 5: August 20, 1918 to November 21, 1919, 1918-19 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Volume 6: December 8, 1919 to April 6, 1920, 1919-20 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Volume 7: April 7 to December 30, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 57)
        Annotated by John Rodker
      - Volume 8: January 3 to July 12, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Volume 9: July 17 to September 6, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - Volume 10: September 28, 1921 to July 2, 1922, 1921-22 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - February 10, 1922 to February 6, 1923 [not numbered], 1922-23
      - Volume 11: October 1924 to December 1925, 1924-25 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Volume 12: December 1925 to [January 1927?], 1925-[27?] (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Volume 13: January 11, 1927 to January 15, 1928, 1927-28 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Volume 14: January 15 to September 9, 1928 (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Volume 15: September 6, 1928 to September 12, 1929, 1928-29 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Volume 15a: February 12 to September 6, 1929, chiefly a record of dreams (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Volume 16: September 15, 1929 to February 3, 1930, 1929-30 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Volume 16a: December 9, 1929 to January 16, 1930, "Gabriel Aitkin's Affairs", 1929-30 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Volume 17: February 13 to May 24, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Volume 18: May 25, 1930 to December 8, 1932, 1930-32 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - Volume 19: December 10, 1932 to May 17, 1936, 1932-36 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - Volume 20: May 18, 1936 to February 27, 1937, 1936-37 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - "Prayers," loose sheet removed from Volume 20, [1936-37] (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Poetry: Bound volumes and related drafts
      - "Legend of the Free Women"
        See also: [Poems, ca. 1913], Box 5, Folder 89
        - Holograph volume, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 74)
        - Typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 75)
        - "Episode" ["Upon the Altar"], typescript, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 76)
        - Holograph fragment, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - "Poems by Mark Drury, July 1911- February 1914"
        - Holograph volume, 1909-14 (Box 5, Folder 78)
          Contains:
          "A Courtesan"
          "A Fragment from Sappho"
          "A Maid's prayer to Artemis Enodiê,
          Our Lady of the Cross Roads"
          "After reading Olive Schreiner's
          Woman and Labour
          "Ad Maiorem Margaritae Gloriam"
          "An Adventure"
          "Ariadne in Naxos"
          "Christmas 1911"
          "Christmas Day 1912"
          "Comrade of Dionysos"
          "Comrades (Kimmeridge Bay)"
          "December 1912"
          "Demeter to Persephone"
          "Dionysiac -- to Hal"
          "G. I., Salterns 1912"
          "Greek Days"
          "Greek Days II"
          "Help me, O my friends"
          "In Italy"
          "In London"
          "Last Prayer"
          "London School of Economics"
          "Megan Myfanwy Owen"
          "M.M.O., Westfield 1911"
          "Our Lady of Wild Things"
          "Sapphics"
          "Spring Song"
          "Spring 1913"
          "Suggested by some of the later poetry
          of Mr. Rudyard Kipling"
          "The Masters"
          "Threnos"
          "To certain of our detractors"
          "To G. I. in rememberence of a weekend
          at Chiswick"
          "To G. I. in S. Africa"
          "To G. I. with the earrings from Cyprus"
          "To my own people (on behalf of G.I.)"
          "Vacation, Christmas 1911"
          "Warbarrow Bay"
          "Westfield, Spring 1912"
        - Typescript of volume, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 79)
          Some pages missing
        - "Dionysiac," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - "Poems by Mark Drury, February 1914--October 1914," second draft
        - Holograph volume, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 81)
          "A Meeting"
          "An Answer?"
          "At the Term's End"
          "British Museum"
          "Dialogue"
          "Dream"
          "In a Boarding-House"
          "In a Tavern"
          "In Hyde Park"
          "In London, Spring 1914"
          "In London XI"
          "In Norway"
          "In the Dark"
          "Nocturne"
          "Nocturne II"
          "On a Motor-Bus"
          "On Badbury Rings"
          "Sunday Afternoon"
          "Spring 1914"
          "To Anthony Butts"
          "To a Young Poet without Money or Health"
          "War Vistas in London"
          "Yesterday" and "Today"
        - "A Meeting," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 82)
        - "An Answer," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 83)
        - "British Museum 1914," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 84)
        - "Dream," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 85)
        - "Nocturne II," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 86)
        - "To Anthony Butts," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 87)
        - "War Vistas in London," typescript carbon (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Untitled [Poems, ca. 1913]
        - Holograph volume, 1913, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 89)
          "A Child's song for the Feast of Anthesteria"
          "A Free Man to a Free Woman"
          "Apollo"
          "Artemis: Victoria Station"
          "Courtesan's Song"
          "Earth's Sacraments"
          "G.I., H.T., M.B."
          "H.T."
          "In London. S."
          "In London. S. Pan"
          "Song of the Boys & Girls"
          "Song of the Married Women"
          "The Birth of Aphrodite"
          "To a Young Lady on Her Approaching Marriage"
          "Wide lies the Kings Way"
          "Within the Sanctuary [...]"
        - "A Child's Song for the Feast of Anthesteria," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 90)
        - "Earth's Sacraments (2)," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 91)
        - "A Free Man to a Free Woman," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 92)
        - "To a Young Lady on her Approaching Marriage," typescript carbon, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - "Poems: Autumn 1915, Winter 1916, Autumn 1917"
        - Holograph volume, 1915-22 (Box 5, Folder 94)
          Contains poems:
          "Inspirations"
          "Isis, & the search for [Osiris?] bite"
          "London, Noon"
          "Rondeau redoublé"
          "Sequels"
          "Vilanella"
          Also contains:
          [Automatic writing]
          "On Modern Art" [essay]
          "Madonna of the Magnificat" [story]
        - "[Sequels] I-III," holograph and typescript (Box 5, Folder 95)
        - "Sequences," typescript carbon, 1917, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - "Poems 1927 (first drafts)"
        - Holograph volume, 1927-30 (Box 5, Folder 97)
          "Antibes" (2)
          "Antigone"
          "At the Boeuf"
          "Cassanova [sic] in Antibes"
          "Dournanez" [sic]
          "Finale"
          "For a Sergey Song"
          "Frère, douce amye"
          "Heartbreak House"
          "Inquiétude"
          "Modern Love"
          "Mother of Croydon to Fairest Comatos"
          "Old Song Improved"
          "On a Young American Girl, who translated
          the Iliad in childhood & came to no good"
          "St. Juan les Pins"
          "Sergey Fragments"
          "Slip of the Moon"
          "Slow"
          "So"
          "The Peace of God"
          "Variations on Heartbreak House"
          "Waiting"